Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Reference Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, reference service records
1907-2018
RU 506
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
390.67
(540 boxes)
The records include research applications; correspondence; guides; donor files; registration forms; files of Thomas Rossiter Barnum; master microforms of the Stimson Papers index and catalog; call slips; ofice of origin request forms; reprographics order forms; and other files concerning reference activities of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives at Yale University Library. The records include the correspondence of the curator of Yale Memorabilia (1907-1933).
Yale University. Library
Related Materials
RU 123, Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, reader services records, circa 1964-2017.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-D (YRG 32-D), Records of Yale school and departmental libraries and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by type of material and in subsequent accessions.
Scope and Contents
The records include research applications; correspondence; guides; donor files; registration forms; files of Thomas Rossiter Barnum; master microforms of the Stimson Papers index and catalog; call slips; ofice of origin request forms; reprographics order forms; and other files concerning reference activities of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives at Yale University Library. The records include the correspondence of the curator of Yale Memorabilia (1907-1933).
Archives; Libraries -- Special collections; Reference services (Libraries); Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and notes of the curator of Yale memorabilia, 1907-1933; Accession 19ND-A-120
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only.
  - A, 1907-1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - B, 1907-1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - C, 1907-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - D, 1907-1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - E-f, 1907-1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - G, 1907-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - H, 1907-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - I J K L, 1907-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - M, 1907-1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - N O P, 1907-1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - R, 1907-1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - S, 1907-1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - T U V, 1907-1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - W, 1907-1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Y, 1907-1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Records concerning Reference Services, pre-1953; Accession 19ND-A-121 (Box 1–6)
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence aranged by collection named and then ordered alphabetically by researcher.
- Records, circa 1953-1974; Accession 19ND-A-122 (Box 1–26)
  No inventory available.
- Correspondence of Dorothy Bridgewater, Accession 19ND-A-123
  - Users
    - A-C (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - D-F (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - G-H (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - I-L (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - M-N (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - O-R (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - S-Z (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stimson applications (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Accession cards (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Acknowledgements
    - A (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - B (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - C-F (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - G-L (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - M-P (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - R-T (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - U-Z (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bibliographies (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cards-reproductions (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Care (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Catalogs - corrections (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Catalog correspondence (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Catalog filings (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Catalog general (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Catalog - union catalog procedures (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Discards (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Distribution rulings (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Distribution readings (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Editing - abbreviations (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Historical manuscripts (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Historical manuscripts and university archives (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - House papers (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Inquiries
    - General (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - A (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Ba-Bn (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bo-Bz (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Boswell (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Bullitt, William C. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Ca-Cl (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Cm-Cz (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - D (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - E (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - F-G (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - G (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - H (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - House, Edward M. (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - I-K (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - L (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Ma-Md (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Me-Mz (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - N-O (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - P (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Q-R (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Sa-Ste (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Sti-Sz (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Silliman (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Stimson, Henry L. (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - T-U (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - V (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - W-Z (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Wharton (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Mason, Franklin (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous autographs (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Manuscript committee, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Manuscritps - general notices (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - National Union Catalog of Manuscript Collections (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - National Union Catalog of Manuscript Collections (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Oriental and AOS (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Photostats (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Photostats (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Reproduction (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Restricted material (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Rules (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Sample letters (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Simkhovitch, V (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Speck (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Stimson Papers (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Theater Guild Collection (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Tocqueville colleciton (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Transfers (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Typewritten lists of manuscripts in Yale library (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Yale (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Agendas
    - 1950-1955 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - 1955-1960 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Agenda mailing list (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Applications (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Kelly - requests (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Library committee, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Papyri (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Paradise - reports (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Pequot Library (Box 6, Folder 91)
- Correspondence, 1960-1973; Accession 19ND-A-125 (Box 1–5)
- Correspondence, 1931-1961; Accession 19ND-A-126 (Box 1)
- Applications, circa 1965-1980; Accession 19ND-A-127 (Box 1–27)
- Applications, circa 1950-1971; Accession 19ND-A-128 (Box 1–37)
  Applications to examine the Henry L. Stimson papers. Arranged alphabetically by name of applicant.
  - A (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - B (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - C (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - D (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - E (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - F (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - G (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - H (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - I (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - J (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - K (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - L (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - M (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - N (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - 0 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - P-Q (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - R (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - S (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - T (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - U-V (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - W (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - X-Z (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Applications, circa 1971-1978; Accession 19ND-A-129 (Box 1–31)
- Reader sign-in registers, 1970-1979; Accession 19ND-A-131
  - Sign-in registers
    - 1970 Oct 29 - 1974 Mar 21 (Box 1)
    - 1974 Mar 21 - 1977 Feb 4 (Box 2)
    - 1974 Feb 4 - 1979 Mar 22 (Box 3)
- Reader registration cards, circa 1976-1982; Accession 19ND-A-138 (Box 1–10)
- Architectural archive reference requests and responses, 1977-1986; Accession 19ND-A-413
  - Research requests, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Correspondence, circa 1977-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6-30)
- Reference correspondence, circa 1930-1959; Accession 19ND-A-415
  The materials are open for research.
  - A (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - B (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - C (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - D-E (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - F-H (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - I-J (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - J (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - M-Q (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - R-S (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - T-W (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Yale, Elihu (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Y-Z (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Y classification shelf list [microfilm], circa 1970; Accession 1970-A-006 (Box 1)
- User slips, circa 1940-1982; Accession 1983-A-098
  Collection contains index cards of donor/provenance files and user slips
  - Donor/provenance cards (Box 1)
  - Records of the use of collections
    Grouped by collection and within each collection arranged alphabetically by patron name.
    - 1969-1972 (Box 2)
    - 1952-1957, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - Account books - Baldwin family papers (Box 4)
    - Balfour - Chester Bowles (Box 5)
    - Bowles, Samuel papers - Civil War Manuscript collection (Box 6)
    - Clap, Thomas papers - Deane, Silas (Box 7)
    - Decision magazine - Evarts family papers (Box 8)
    - Fabrique family - Griswold, A. Whitney (Box 9)
    - Hadley, Arthur - House, Edward M. Papers (Box 10)
    - House, Edward M. Papers - Knollenberg (Box 11)
    - Labree family - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 12)
    - Madison - Munger, Thornton Taft (Box 13)
    - Nagle, Charles papers - Pierrpont, Edwards (Box 14)
    - Poe - Ruskin, John (Box 15)
    - Saarinen, Eero papers - Stein, Gertrude (Box 16)
    - Stein, Leo - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Box 17)
    - Stokes, Rose Pator - Twombly (Box 18)
    - Uberti, Ubaldo D. - Wilder, John Augustus (Box 19)
    - Wilder, Thonton - Yale Manuscripts and Misc. Manuscripts (Box 20)
    - Yale Univesity Archives: Medical School - Zoology Department (Box 21)
- Biographical reference correspondence, circa 1970-1983; Accession 1983-A-099
  This material consists of the carbons of replies to various reference letters. The letters are all biographical - about Yale men. Carbons are arranged alphabetically by last name of the Yale individual. Correspondence dates mostly from the 1970-1983 with some earlier materials.
  - General (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ba-Bo (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Br-Bz (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bush, George (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ca-Cn (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Co-Cz (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - D (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - E-F (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - G (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ha-Hi (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ho-Hz (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - I-K (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - L (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - M (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - N-O (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Pa-Ph (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Pl-Q (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - R (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Sa-Sl (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sm-Sz (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ta-Tg (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Th-Tz (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - U-V (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Wa-Wh (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Wi-Wz (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Y-Z (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Registration cards, circa 1982-1983; Accession 1983-A-100
  - Reader registration cards (A - Z), 1982 June - 1983 May (Box 1–2)
- Chronological files, circa 1975-1982; Accession 1983-A-101 (Box 1–4)
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Research requests, 1975-1982; Accession 1983-A-102 (Box 1)
- Manuscript applications, 1978-1982; Accession 1983-A-103
  - Aa - Bf (Box 1)
  - Bg - Bz (Box 2)
  - Ca - Cp (Box 3)
  - Cq - Ez (Box 4)
  - Fa - Gf (Box 5)
  - Gg - Hh (Box 6)
  - Hi - J (Box 7)
  - Ka - Kz (Box 8)
  - La - Mac (Box 9)
  - Mad - Mz (Box 10)
  - Na - Pg (Box 11)
  - Ph - Rt (Box 12)
  - Ru - Se (Box 13)
  - Sf - Ste (Box 14)
  - Stf - V (Box 15)
  - Wa - Wk (Box 16)
  - WI - Z (Box 17)
  - Yale University Dean's Offices Requests for Student Folders
    - 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Completed, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Completed President's Office Requests, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Dean's Files Completed, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - University Requests (Various), 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Photo Order Forms, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Completed Loans, 1976-77 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Photo Order Foms, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Xerox Orders, Book Material, (No Applications), 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Book Xerox Orders, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Completed Research Requests, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Photo Orders Without Applications, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Manuscript applications, 1983-1984; Accession 1984-A-061
  - A, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Be, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bf-Bz, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ca-Cn, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Co-Cz, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - D, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - E, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - F, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ga-Gk, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gl-Gz, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ha-Hh, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hi-Hz, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - I, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - J, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - K, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - L, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mc, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ma-Mo, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mp-Mz, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - N, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - O, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - P, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Q, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - R, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sa-Sl, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Sm-Sp, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - St-Sz, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Ta-Th, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ti-Tz, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - U-V, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Wa, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - We-Wh, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Wi-Wz, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Y, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Z, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Office of Origins, June 1983-May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Permission to publish A-F, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Permission to publish G-O, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Permission to publish P-Z, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1974-1983; Accession 1984-A-062
  - A, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Aa-Ae, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Af-Alg, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alh-AmChem, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Am Embassy, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Am. Her-And., 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ane-Ap, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Ar-Ash, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ask-Au, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Av-Az, 1974-83 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - B-BK, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Baa-Bak, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Bal-Bar, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Bas-Bat, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bam-Bea, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Beb-Be1, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bem-Beq, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Ber-Bez, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bf-Bishop, Ch, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Bishop, Courtney, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Bishop, Jo-Bk, 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - BL-BUS, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Bl-Blod, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bloms-Bn, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Boa-Bon, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Boo-Boz, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Bra-Brc, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Brd-Bril, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Brim-Brot, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Brou-Borw, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Brox-Buh, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Bui-Bus, 1974-83 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - BUT-COLK, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - But-Bz, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Caa-Cameron, Ch, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Camf-Cark, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Carl-Cars, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Amon Carter Museum, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Carter-CBS, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - CBS-60 Minutes, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Ce-Center, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - CRL, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Centr-Cha, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Che-Chz, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Ci-Clarke, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Clraki-Clz, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Cm-Colk, 1974-83 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - COLL-DEM, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Coll-Con, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Coo-Coq, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Cor-Cov, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Cow-Cran, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Crao-Crz, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Cs-Curs, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Curt-Cz, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Daa-Dam, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Dan-Davie, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Davin-Deb, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Dec-Dem, 1974-83 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - DEN-EL, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Den-Dest, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Detroit Institute of Art, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Detw-Dez, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Df-Di, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Dj-Doe, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Doe-Dq, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Dr-Dt, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Dua-Duo, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Dup-Dz, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Ea-Eh, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - El-El, 1974-83 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - EM-FZ, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Em-Et, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Eu-Evans, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Evar-Ez, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Fa-Fc, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Fd-Fen, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Feo-Fie, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Fif-Fiz, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Fj-Foq, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - For-Fq, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Fr-Fred, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Freedman, Lila, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Freedman, R-FT, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Fu-Fz, 1974-83 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - G, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Gaa-Gas, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Gat-Gh, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Gia Gilk, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Gill-Glen, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Gli-Goq, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Gor-Grea, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Greb-Greh, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Grei-Grir, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Gris-Gz, 1974-83 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - HAA-HIQ, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Haa-Hall, Q, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Hall, R-Hanj, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Hank-Harris, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Harrison-Hat, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Hau-Hd, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Hea-Hem, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Hen-Hh, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Hia-Hiq, 1974-83 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - HIR-JOM, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Hir-Hok, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Hol-Hon, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Hoo-Houg, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Hous-Ht, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Hu-Hv, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Hw-Hz, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - I, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Jaa-Jae, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Jaffe, Irma, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Jaf-Jh, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Ji-Jom, 1974-83 (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - JON-KZ, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Jon-Judd, E., 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Judd, Mrs. Frances, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Judd, J-Kd., 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Kea-Kel, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Kem-Kerb, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Kerb-Kiq, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Kir-Knh, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Kni-Kom, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Kon-Kt, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Ku-Kz, 1974-83 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - L, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 131)
    - Laa-Lam, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Lan-Laq, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 133)
    - Lar-Ld, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 134)
    - Leo-Lh, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Lia-Lio, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 136)
    - Lip-Loether, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 137)
    - Loewenwanther-Loq, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - Lor-Luc, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Lud-Lz, 1974-83 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - MAA-Miller, I, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 142)
    - Maa-McC, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 143)
    - McD-McK, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 144)
    - McL-Mad, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 145)
    - Mae-Maq, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 146)
    - Mara-Mars, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 147)
    - Mart-Maw, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 148)
    - May-Maz, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Mb-Mh, 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Mia-Miller, I., 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Miller, J. - Nev, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - Miller, J.-Mim, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 153)
    - Min-Mn, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - Moa-Moom, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 155)
    - Moon-Morf, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - Morg-Morr, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 157)
    - Mors-Muq, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 158)
    - Mur-Mz, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 159)
    - Na-Nd, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - Nea-Nev, 1974-83 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - NEW-PAS, 1974-83 (Box 15, Folder 162)
    - New-Nn, 1974-83 (Box 15, Folder 163)
    - No-Nz, 1974-83 (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - Oa-Ok, 1974-83 (Box 15, Folder 165)
    - Ol-Oq, 1974-83 (Box 15, Folder 166)
    - Or-Oz, 1974-83 (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Paa-Pan, 1974-83 (Box 15, Folder 168)
    - Pape-Pas, 1974-83 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - PAT-RAS, 1974-83 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Pat-Pep, 1974-83 (Box 16, Folder 172)
    - Per-Ph, 1974-83 (Box 16, Folder 173)
    - Pi-Pk, 1974-83 (Box 16, Folder 174)
    - PI-Pos, 1974-83 (Box 16, Folder 175)
    - Pot-Pz, 1974-83 (Box 16, Folder 176)
    - Q, 1974-83 (Box 16, Folder 177)
    - Raa-Ras, 1974-83 (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - RAT-RZ, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 179)
    - Rat-Reh, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - Rei-Reg, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 181)
    - Rh-Ric, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 182)
    - Rid-Riz, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 183)
    - RLG Requests, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 184)
    - Roa-Rod, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 185)
    - Roe-Rosenblurn, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 186)
    - Rosenblum, Stewart, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 187)
    - Rosenfeld-Rt, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - Rua-Rur, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - Rus-Rz, 1974-83 (Box 17, Folder 190)
  - SAA-SIL, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 191)
    - Saa-Sare, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 192)
    - Sargent, Henry B., 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 193)
    - Sarl-Schd, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 194)
    - Sche-Schm, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 195)
    - Schn-Schv, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 196)
    - Schw-Sd, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 197)
    - Sea-Shaq, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 198)
    - Shar-Shh, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 199)
    - Shi-Sil, 1974-83 (Box 18, Folder 200)
  - SIM-STOJ, 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 201)
    - Sim-Sk, 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 202)
    - Sl-Smith, L., 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 203)
    - Smith, Me-Sob, 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 204)
    - Society of Architectural Historians, 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 205)
    - Soc-Ss, 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 206)
    - Sta-Std, 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 207)
    - Stea-Stein, L., 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 208)
    - Stein Me -Stev, 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 209)
    - Stew-Stoj, 1974-83 (Box 19, Folder 210)
  - STOK-TT, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 211)
    - Stok-Stz, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 212)
    - Su-Swd, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 213)
    - Swe-Sz, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 214)
    - Ta-Tc, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 215)
    - Th-Time, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 216)
    - Time-Life Books, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 217)
    - Timm-Tol, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 218)
    - Tom-Tt, 1974-83 (Box 20, Folder 219)
  - TU-WEH, 1974-83 (Box 21, Folder 220)
    - Tu-Tz, 1974-83 (Box 21, Folder 221)
    - U, 1974-83 (Box 21, Folder 222)
    - Va-Vek, 1974-83 (Box 21, Folder 223)
    - Vel-Vz, 1974-83 (Box 21, Folder 224)
    - Waa-Wala, 1974-83 (Box 21, Folder 225)
    - Wald-War, 1974-83 (Box 21, Folder 227)
    - Was-Weh, 1974-83 (Box 21, Folder 228)
  - WEI-WQ, 1974-83 (Box 22, Folder 229)
    - Wei-Wes, 1974-83 (Box 22, Folder 230)
    - Wet-Whe, 1974-83 (Box 22, Folder 231)
    - Whia-White, G., 1974-83 (Box 22, Folder 232)